And that's treasonous, probably.
So if you could, if you, very important,
if you could do that, it would be great.
Nobody would know better than you.
You'll figure it out.
Thank you.
Please, go ahead.
Yeah, my name's Nick Shirley.
I'm 23 years old.
I'm 100% independent YouTube journalist.
And over the past year or so, I've
been able to go to 15 countries.
I've hung out with people in the gangs of Brazil
in the favelas, in the prisons of Central.
But yet, the most dangerous places I have been
have been here in the United States, unfortunately.
And I've had the opportunity to show people about the protest
antifa here in the United States.
And there's nothing organic about what they are doing here
in the United States.
I've watched people be bused in from states.
I've watched the same lady at a protest in Atlanta
be bused to protest in DC, and then in New York City.
There's nothing that is honest about what they are doing.
And they have signs.
I've seen the same signs here in DC and in London as well.
It's a big organization, incorporation
that they're running.
And people may wonder, what's the threat to us
as Americans if we go?
Well, you'll be labeled as a fascist.
You'll be labeled as a Nazi.
And they'll wish death upon you, because they
wish death upon me.
And just last week in Portland, Oregon,
I watched a lady get trapped in her car, surrounded by antifa.
And her sister messaged me after seeing the video.
She said, the only reason I think my sister was safe
was because you were there recording me.
I also was chased out by a member of antifa
who said he would smoke me.
And next thing he knew, a DHS sniper had lasers on his chest.
If he was not there, who knows what
would have happened that day?
These people are very dangerous.
And people wonder how they're able to do it.
The reason is because these cities are not
enforcing the law.
And why should these people be worried if the law is not
being enforced?
And we are not far right, nor are we far wrong.
We're just right.
And the truth about what's happening here in America
with these groups is very dangerous.
And I thank you, Mr. President, and your administration
as well for acknowledging that.
Thank you very much.
It's too bad you have to go through it.
I know.
It's a little crazy, right, Mr. President?
When you're going to get to the bottom of it.
So it's a very important thing you're doing.
Thank you very much.
Please, Kim.
Yeah, I've just got something very short.
I'm attacked every time I do my job.
When I leave my house to go to work, I am violently assaulted.
I've had guns pulled on me.
I've been bear sprayed.
I've been beaten down.
I've been almost killed.
So my question for all of you is, how would you feel?